

Cristiano Louriceira Martins

💌 cristianomartins96@hotmail.com 📞 +351.911834635 👂 Amiais de Baixo, Portugal 🚗 B / B1

Profile

Academically, I have a degree in "Geography and Regional Planning", Master in "Territory Management with specialization in Remote Sensing and Geographic Information Systems" and some experience in cartographic production (in non-curricular internship). Currently I work as a simplified registration technician (BUPi). In addition to the above, during the period of the COVID-19 pandemic I started to develop skills as a web programmer. Skills that I improve to this day.

That being said, consider visiting my website:

https://cristianolm.github.io/presentation/ ☑

Professional Experience

Simplified registry technician (Bupi),

07/2023 - present

Socarto - Sociedade De Levantamentos Topo Cartográficos, Lda. 🛭 Mapping of rustic and mixed properties in a GIS environment.

Temporary collaboration, The USE Concept, Lda.

12/2019 - 03/2020

Update of characterization and diagnostic studies, for review of the PDM of Caldas da Rainha.

Lisbon, Portugal

Internship, The USE Concept, Lda.

02/2019 - 08/2019

Lisbon, Portugal

Review of PDM's and topographic cartography update.

- Conversion of CAD data to GIS in order to build a database, to be used in the production of base cartography;
- Support to report writing;
- Data acquisition;
- Cartographic editing;
- Quality control;
- Field completion.

Internship, CICS.NOVA

07/2017 - 08/2017

Internship in Interdisciplinary Center for Social Sciences at the NOVA University of Lisbon and two publications.

Lisbon, Portugal

Publication links ☑

Sporadic jobs 2012 - present

- Auto Painter Helper (Amiais de Baixo (Portugal))
- Factory worker (Indutan // Comércio e Indústria de Peles, S.A.., Amiais de Cima (Portugal);

- Strawberry plantation (Herdade da Fragaria, Amiais de Baixo (Portugal));
- Grape picking (Malaqueijo (Portugal));
- · Pear picking;

Education

Master in Territory Management with specialization in Remote Sensing and Geographic Information Systems,

10/2019 – 03/2021 Lisbon, Portugal

Faculty of Social and Human Sciences at NOVA University of Lisbon

Master thesis ☑

Minor in International Relations,

03/2018 - 06/2018

Faculty of Social and Human Sciences at NOVA University of Lisbon

Graduation in Geography and Regional Planning,

Faculty of Social and Human Sciences at NOVA University of Lisbon

10/2015 - 06/2018

Lisbon, Portugal

Skills

Microsoft Office

● ● ● ● GIS Software

Word - Excel - PowerPoint ArcMap - eCognition - QGIS

Version Control System

● ● ● ● ● Web programming

GIT HTML - CSS - JavaScript/TypeScript - React - GIT/Github - MariaDB/MySQL.

Courses

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux), Udemy ☑

The Complete Quality Assurance Course- Learn QA from Scratch, *Udemy* ☑

Javascript Tutorial and Projects Course (2022), Udemy □

The Git & Github Bootcamp, *Udemy* ☑

The Ultimate MySQL Bootcamp: Go from SQL Beginner to Expert, Udemy ☑

The Linux Command Line Bootcamp: Beginner To Power User, Udemy ☑

Programador Web Full-Stack, *Codemaster* ☑

Canguages

• Portuguese • English